{"metadata":{"generator":"Captivate","generatorVersion":"11.8.0","schemaVersion":"","author":"author","title":"","description":"project description","email":"author@company.com","website":"www.company.com","tags":"","thumbnail":"","source":"assets","durationInFrames":1560,"frameRate":30,"totalSlides":10,"width":970,"height":535,"responsive":false,"scalable":false,"launchFile":"index.html","isVRProject":false},"contentStructure":[{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_5","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_5","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["IRRPA"]},"constraints":{"length":5}}}},{"id":"SmartShape_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_2","title":"In the “Trans ID” field, enter IRRPA to reach the “RECEIVING SELECT CRITERIA” screen. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_2","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_6","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_6","title":"Click the white box and type IRRPA. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_6","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_6","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide7911","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Entry_Box_5","SmartShape_2","Success_Shape_2","Hint_Shape_6","Failure_Shape_6"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":150},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide7911"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_3","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_3","title":"In the “Purchase Order” field, type the Purchase Order number (7687885). ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_6","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_6","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["7687885"]},"constraints":{"length":7}}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_3","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_3","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_7","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_7","title":"Click the white box and type 7687885. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_7","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_7","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide7971","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_3","Text_Entry_Box_6","Success_Shape_3","Hint_Shape_7","Failure_Shape_7"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":150},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide7971"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_4","title":"A response message will appear, type Y for “Yes” and press Enter to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_7","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_7","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["Y"]},"constraints":{"length":1}}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_4","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_8","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_8","title":"Click the white box and type Y then press Enter. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_8","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_8","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8004","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_4","Text_Entry_Box_7","Success_Shape_4","Hint_Shape_8","Failure_Shape_8"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":150},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8004"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_5","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_5","title":"A response message will appear, type Y for “Yes” and press Enter to create an appointment. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_8","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_8","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["Y"]},"constraints":{"length":1}}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_5","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_5","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_9","title":"Click the white box and type Y then press Enter. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_9","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8037","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_5","Text_Entry_Box_8","Success_Shape_5","Hint_Shape_9","Failure_Shape_9"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":150},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8037"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_6","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_6","title":"The “Appointment” and “Date & Time” fields will populate. Press Enter to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_9","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":[]},"constraints":{"length":1}}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_10","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_10","title":"Press the Enter key. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8063","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_6","Text_Entry_Box_9","Hint_Shape_10"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":150},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8063"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_9","title":"Enter the door number (001)  in the “Door” field and press Enter. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_10","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_10","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["001"]},"constraints":{"length":3}}}},{"id":"SmartShape_16","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_16","title":"Note that the cursor will automatically move to the “Trace” field after entering the door number. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_6","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_6","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_11","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_11","title":"Click the white box and type 001 then press Enter. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_10","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_10","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8123","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_9","Text_Entry_Box_10","SmartShape_16","Success_Shape_6","Hint_Shape_11","Failure_Shape_10"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":210},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8123"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_10","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_10","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_11","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_11","title":"Press the Tab key to reach the “Data-Entry” section and press Enter. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_11","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_11","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":[]},"constraints":{"length":1}}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_12","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_12","title":"Press the Tab key, then press Enter. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8156","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_10","SmartShape_11","Text_Entry_Box_11","Hint_Shape_12"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":150},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8156"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_12","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_12","title":"Review the data, and press Enter to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_12","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_12","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":[]},"constraints":{"length":1}}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_13","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_13","title":"Press the Enter key. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8216","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_12","Text_Entry_Box_12","Hint_Shape_13"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":150},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8216"}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_14","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_14","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":[]},"constraints":{"length":1}}}},{"id":"SmartShape_13","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_13","title":"Press the Tab key to reach the “Totals” screen and press Enter to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_14","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_14","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_15","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_15","title":"Press the Enter key. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8276","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Entry_Box_14","SmartShape_13","SmartShape_14","Hint_Shape_15"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":150},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8276"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_15","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_15","title":"Press Enter to complete the Purchase Order. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_15","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_15","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":[]},"constraints":{"length":1}}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_16","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_16","title":"Press the Enter key. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8340","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_15","Text_Entry_Box_15","Hint_Shape_16"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":150},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8340"}}},{"id":"Pool423","class":"pool","roles":{"pool":{"id":423,"name":"Pool1","questions":[]}}},{"id":"OpenPOIRRPAtraining","class":"project","title":"OpenPOIRRPAtraining","children":["Slide7911","Slide7971","Slide8004","Slide8037","Slide8063","Slide8123","Slide8156","Slide8216","Slide8276","Slide8340"],"roles":{"quiz":{"id":379,"branched":false,"submitAll":false,"review":true,"questions":[],"minScore":0,"maxScore":0,"passScore":0}}}],"contentSettings":{"global":{"branchAware":false},"toc":{"enabled":false},"playbar":{"enabled":true,"cc":false,"playPause":true,"back":true,"forward":true,"rewind":true,"close":true,"mute":true,"progressBar":true}},"contentReporting":{"CCCriteria":"launch_content","SCCriteria":"launch_content","exitNormalIfCompleted":false},"toc":[{"id":"Slide7911","title":"Slide 1"},{"id":"Slide7971","title":"Slide 2"},{"id":"Slide8004","title":"Slide 3"},{"id":"Slide8037","title":"Slide 4"},{"id":"Slide8063","title":"Slide 5"},{"id":"Slide8123","title":"Slide 6"},{"id":"Slide8156","title":"Slide 7"},{"id":"Slide8216","title":"Slide 8"},{"id":"Slide8276","title":"Slide 9"},{"id":"Slide8340","title":"Slide 10"}]}